{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"8807/41",
			"answer":"8807/41",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5776/75",
			"answer":"5776/75",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5216/19",
			"answer":"5216/19",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4922/83",
			"answer":"4922/83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7526/45",
			"answer":"7526/45",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.96/0.58",
			"answer":"6.96/0.58",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.968/0.53",
			"answer":"2.968/0.53",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1760/0.88",
			"answer":"1760/0.88",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"31.64/0.48",
			"answer":"31.64/0.48",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1600/50",
			"answer":"1600/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}